We have an indication from the NEO Campus Ministries. Mr. Steve Whiteill,
Bless this community and she's just named up right.
On the four public input, our unscheduled personal appearances five consent agenda staff recommends we approve item six
and seven. Motion to approve?
And Tyler wrote a statement on this. See the fuel man charges here as peats ever got where he can use to new pizza now everything I've talked about it continues
To be underlifts according arresting, continue
Continue being underlist and you want do that right
The only piece is one out by turn point gig isn't for few men
At all at these time
Thank many points should have if your get gas there or did
You get gas out there though, yeah
Did you got like a whole bunch of points don't do
How can I?
My phone trust
Do my phones try
He gets point for all the drinks that he gives for those guys
Dinner is still here
But that happens to hear stays here breath
The people in there brag about how many points he's got
Yeah, you guys are like more point. See my neighbor machine
Okay
That is for the 120 road
We'll submit it to you out once its approved or if approve of reimbursement
They usually like us finish off a project and then send that as one packet
So there's chance I don't be reimbursed. Oh, There’s no chances they will be reversed
Yeah i mean
Okay
yeah
We’re going back into private so we're buying
You'll see as much things some easements here before home to go
That's the nice thing about being a private isn't that is
When they read why in high order whatever make it come pay you for everything
What are trying
Thankyou
Most proof
I don’t vote
Hi
Eight Davis right
For Pinscolour, GRDA Relicensing and associate complaint
Proceedings in the amount of 93,635
So this is an actual combination about three months of claims
It goes back to December 1st
We’ve got all it's been on January and February
There’s 3 separate ones so that sall combined
Through t time as you can imagine
That encompasses a lot
We’re going to have a prep work for and around the updated study report
The actual most current studying reports that GRDA presented
And then review in comments of that’s Study Report
That were submitted
To Fart from city
In other tribes, we also reviewed
Within debriefing after the studied report
So there’s prep and debriefing
We’re 16th we had our town home
At that time, hometeen
And then a prep study of citizen questions and gathering information
Then prepping important together with the power points
To review it actually for people here in having a town hall
After that’s done
That same timeframe
In January February
The draft license, submitted by GRDA
And so there was quite a bit of effort around that
Review
Of their draft report
The draft license application as well as comb it
A lot activity has been going on
Great deal with detail
I know we could probably talk about it in greater detail
If you want to, but maybe be an executive session
Just because and alot
We’re getting into the actual legal strategy
And so legal matters of this nature
We try to keep them somewhat high level
With that I’d be happy
To answer any questions i could
But if we want a detailed detail and know that’s alot
If you wanted it, go ahead
That’s really about
It is 3 months worth of invoices
Why did the three month?
What are they doing?
They are doing a lot of work
We’ve had so much activity lately
Once they build them and we got him
There was no particular issue around that
From the funding side
After this, in there
That were trying to explain
The 750.000 that we budgeted
This fiscal year
We paid this invoice
If you all approved the invoice
You still have remaining 410,000 in that budget
So we had funding available for it
Budget ends June
The invoices I’ve seen
They haven’t not been seeing any of these
But they are saying the same
The last one was like 3900
So these are probably the last of
The big ones for quite a while
Maybe not even through this year
We’re really minimal
I’ll make it much away
I will sign up
I don’t know what you say
No, remember random
I’ve understand with the river of bottom
Sportsman’s association for disabled veterans
Been there, has quarantined
He is on speaker here on phone
I’ve initially had there
Been opening ceremony, downtown
Which included the raising of a giant American flag
On building
Jack Downman pulled a used arm
But that’s not owned now
Now we’re all going to another business
And they are operating at it
So you can’t raise the flag
What they’re wanted to do is move
The inter-
Opening ceremonies and flag raising
Jack Downman pulls property
Which creates new problems for
Well, look when we back out there
They need it directly structured
But it’s big enough that things can raise the flag
There are asking us for help in building that
There’s no problem in the city
I’ve worked on climate profit
And so we’re doing this through an M.O., new
With the river of bottom, sportsmen
From Lowing Man
We are helping them, build the structures
We need to plant some telephone poles
They're providing the poles, all they were doing
The poles in the hole
This event is everybody as well
Where it’s a big attraction
And it’s source
They give up, we’ll see you by that
So stay afestrate
I will be happy to meet you
Hold my promotion
Say it
Hi
Thank You Jack
And Shannon for what you guys do
I'm glad we can be a little small part of that
So, I’m 10
By the new business event which is a residence in the post office at Indy
11 staff reports
12 trustee community announcements
13 adjournment
I think you will
Williams
Hi